good morning good afternoon and good
早上好，下午好
evening wherever you may happen to be in
晚上，无论您可能碰巧在哪里
the world thank you so much for joining
世界非常感谢您的加入
me spring and pivotal webinar program
我的春季和关键网络研讨会计划
again we're excited to have you back and
再次，我们很高兴您能回来
I am your MC is always Peter Humphrey
我是您的MC永远是Peter Humphrey
and I have the distinct pleasure today
我今天很高兴
of introducing a lead committer for the
引入首席提交人
spring boot project to celebrate our
spring boot 项目来庆祝我们
spring boot - OH
spring boot -OH
release Philip Webb from pivotal and we
释放Philip Webb的关键地位，我们
are also joined during the question and
在问题期间也加入了
answer by spring blue team members
春季蓝色团队成员的回答
mother above a and andy wilkinson so
母亲以上安迪·威尔金森所以
Phil um you know I know I told you I'd
菲尔，你知道我知道我告诉过你我会
help you out with slides today but
今天帮助您制作幻灯片，但是
you're not using any slides so uh no not
您没有使用任何幻灯片，所以不
today
今天
yeah so this is pretty awesome um this
是的，所以这很棒
is your typical Rockstar performance
是典型的摇滚明星表演
that you've done at Spring one so we're
您已经在春季第一期完成了，所以我们
excited to have you and thanks thanks
很高兴有你，谢谢
for thanks for being willing to do this
感谢您愿意这样做
um why don't you tell us a little bit
嗯，你为什么不告诉我们一点
about the about the release and things
关于发布和事情
that you've got you excited yeah so
令你兴奋的是的
we've we've just cut a spring boot - oh
我们已经剪了一个 spring boot -哦
it was kind of not too many issues which
这不是太多的问题
is pretty good we're planning to do a
很好，我们正计划做一个
201 in the next couple of weeks or so
在接下来的两周左右中会出现201
things things seem to be generally going
事情似乎总在进行
ok I've got lots to show you in this
好的，我有很多东西要向你展示
presentation so it's going to think
演示文稿，所以它会思考
about an hour and I'm going to do
大约一个小时，我要去做
something slightly different I'm going
我要去的东西有些不同
to take a I'm going to start with a
拿一个我要开始一个
spring boot warm five application and
spring boot 保暖五应用
try and show you the steps that you need
尝试向您展示所需的步骤
to follow if you want to upgrade it to
如果要升级到
spring boot - and then we're going to
spring boot -然后我们要
move that app forwards and actually make
向前移动该应用程序并实际进行
it into a fully reactive application
使其成为完全反应的应用程序
using web hooks that sounds awesome but
使用网络挂钩听起来很棒，但
I mean I've heard that people only
我的意思是我只听说过人
needed to know that we support an ASCII
需要知道我们支持ASCII
animated art banners in order to really
动画艺术横幅才能真正
know I'm grandma I'm not I decided
知道我是奶奶，不是我决定
against doing that it just it just it
反对这样做，只是它而已
felt like it was it was just too good to
感觉就像是太好了
share on a on a webinar we have you have
在网络研讨会上分享我们
to see that live I'm afraid all right I
看到那场直播我很担心我
hear you
听到你
I totally hear you go you got to come to
我完全听见你走了，你必须来
spring one for that one all right so
为那一个 Spring 好一点
will please take it away okay
请把它拿走好吗
right so what I've got here I said said
对，所以我在这里说
earlier is I'm going to start with a
较早的时候，我将从一个
spring boot one five application so I
spring boot 一五应用程序，所以我
just got a really kind of simple
真的很简单
application with just enough moving
移动足够的应用程序
parts to kind of show some of the the
部分显示一些
issues that you're likely to face when
您可能会遇到的问题
you upgrade so let's start by looking at
您进行升级，因此让我们先来看一下
the palm so you can see here we are on
手掌，所以你可以看到我们在这里
spring boot one five ten release and we
spring boot 一五十发布，我们
have a few dependencies we're using
有一些依赖我们正在使用
spring boots start of web which is going
Web的 spring boot 开始
to give us Tomcat and spring MVC we have
给我们Tomcat和spring MVC，我们有
the actuator which is going to give us
将给我们的执行器
sort of metrics and monitoring and all
各种指标和监控以及所有
that good stuff we are using security
我们正在使用安全性的好东西
and we also have MongoDB as our back-end
而且我们还有MongoDB作为我们的后端
database and the reason I've picked
数据库以及我选择的原因
MongoDB is because MongoDB is one of the
MongoDB是因为MongoDB是其​​中之一
few that we have actually got reactive
我们实际上很少有反应
support for so there's about three or
支持，所以大约有三个或
four that we have reactive support
四，我们有反应性的支持
there's reactive drivers available so
有可用的被动驱动程序
Mongo makes a good good choice for this
蒙哥为此做出了很好的选择
demo and what else we got we've got this
演示，还有什么我们得到的
flapdoodle thing which gives us embedded
扑通扑通的东西，这给我们嵌入
Mongo which just means I don't have to
Mongo，这意味着我不必
bother installing it and then some test
麻烦安装它，然后进行一些测试
dependencies which we might actually be
我们可能实际上是的依赖
using today and then at the bottom we
使用今天，然后在底部，我们
also have the spring boot maven plug-in
也有spring boot maven插件
and a git commit plugin it's just going
还有一个git commit插件
to give us some get char information
给我们一些获取字符信息
when we run this app ok we have a quick
当我们运行这个程序好，我们有一个快速
look at the code just so you familiar
看一下代码，让您熟悉
with the application so we have webinar
与应用程序，所以我们有网络研讨会
application which is just a kind of
应用程序只是一种
entry point doesn't really do anything
入口点并没有真正做任何事情
other than setups the spring boot
除了设置 spring boot
shenanigans so we have a spring boot
shenanigans，所以我们有一个 spring boot
annotation and the main method we then
注释和主要方法
have a couple of controller so we then
有几个控制器，所以我们然后
have a some domain objects so this city
有一些领域的对象，所以这个城市
object here is a Mongo document and it's
这里的对象是一个Mongo文档，它是
just got two fields name and country and
刚得到两个字段名称和国家
then we have a city repository which is
然后我们有一个城市仓库
a string
一个字符串
data repository that's just giving us a
数据仓库只是给我们一个
couple of methods to get access to those
几种访问这些方法的方法
those Mongo documents so we have find
这些Mongo文件，所以我们找到了
all which will give us everything and we
所有这些都会给我们一切，我们
have find by name ignoring case which
已经找到名字忽略大小写
will give us one city given its name and
会给我们一个城市的名字
then the only other kind of slightly
然后只有另一种
unusual part of this application is we
此应用程序不寻常的部分是我们
need to get data into this repository so
需要将数据放入该存储库，以便
what I've decided to do is I decided to
我决定要做的是
use a yam or file so here we have a list
使用山药或文件，所以这里有一个列表
of cities so this is the test data that
的城市，所以这是测试数据
we're going to populate the database
我们将填充数据库
with when it starts up and I wanted to
当它启动时，我想
kind of make use of a class that is in
有点用在
spring boot 1/5 but isn't in spring boot
spring boot 1/5，但不在 spring boot 中
2 just to show you that depending on
2只是为了向您展示
like how deeply you integrate with
就像你与之融合的深度
spring boot there there may be some kind
spring boot 可能有某种
of changes that you need to meet with
您需要应对的变化
your code so this is slightly atypical
您的代码，所以这有点不典型
but it kind of gives you an idea of
但这给你一个想法
things that you might need to change so
你可能需要改变的事情
just looking at this far we have load
只是看了这么远，我们有负载
city's llamo so this thing basically
城市的llamo所以这东西基本上
takes this is Spring Framework class
这是Spring Framework类
that lets you load yeah mall and make it
可以让您加载购物中心并做到
look like a properties object so this
看起来像一个属性对象，所以这
will load up that cities the animal farm
将装载那个城市的动物农场
once we've got that in we kind of adapt
一旦有了，我们就可以适应
it to this mutable property sources
它到这个可变的财产来源
thing sorry we add it to a mutable
抱歉，我们将其添加到可变对象中
property sources we then use this
财产来源，然后我们用这个
relaxed data binder which is a spring
轻松的数据绑定器，是 Spring
boot 1/5 concern and we are binding the
启动1/5的关注，我们正在约束
values that we got from the amyl to this
从戊基到这个的值
object called cities which we really
我们称之为城市的对象
just need to get a list of city objects
只需获取城市对象的列表
out so this is like a little bit
出来，所以这有点像
convoluted and complicated but it's it's
令人费解和复杂，但这是
done for a reason so that when we
这样做是有原因的，所以当我们
upgrade you can see the differences yep
升级您可以看到差异
so that's that's pretty much it this
所以就是这个
relaxed binder thing if you've used
如果您曾经使用过轻松的活页夹
configuration properties in the past
过去的配置属性
this is the class that's responsible for
这是负责的课程
kind of setting those up when you run
在您运行时进行设置
your application so this is what spring
您的应用程序，这就是 Spring
but--one 5 uses behind the scenes
但是-有5种用途在幕后
okay yeah I'm not going to update my ID
好的，我不会更新我的ID
right now so if you run this up
现在，所以如果你运行这个
hopefully it's not so I can show you a
希望不是，所以我可以告诉你
couple of endpoints we've got this this
几个端点，我们有这个
little view here is part of Firefox it
这里的小视图是Firefox的一部分
just presents a JSON a nice way so this
只是提供了一个JSON的好方法，所以这
is the raw JSON
是原始JSON
this is the view that I'll kind of show
这就是我要展示的观点
most of the time so you can see here
大多数时候，所以你可以在这里看到
we've got the cities being response if
我们得到了城市的回应，如果
we like look for all of them or if we
我们喜欢寻找所有的人，或者如果我们
want to look for like a single city like
想要寻找像一个城市一样
so and then there's just a single piece
所以只有一块
of data so not much to the app let me
的数据对应用程序没有太多影响
just show you one one or two other
只给你看一两个
things the city's thing we're doing a
我们正在做的事情
little bit of java 8 style streaming and
Java 8风格的流式传输的一点点
filtering so we're only showing cities
过滤，因此我们只显示城市
that are in the USA again that's for a
再次在美国是为了
specific reason now I'll come on to
现在我要讲的具体原因
later and then if we have a quick look
以后再看一下
at the application properties we can see
在应用程序属性中，我们可以看到
we set up some application info which is
我们设置了一些应用程序信息
something that will appear in the
将会出现在
actuator later this is just some Mongo
执行器，这只是一些Mongo
stuff and then there are two settings
东西，然后有两个设置
here that we need we need to be
在这里，我们需要我们需要成为
concerned about one is we set a password
关注一个是我们设置密码
so we don't have to keep remembering it
所以我们不必一直记住它
and the other is we're turning off basic
另一个是我们要关闭基本
security for the application so that
应用程序的安全性
just our actuator endpoints need
只是我们的执行器端点需要
security so if I go back over here and
安全，所以如果我回到这里
look at the info actuator endpoint you
看看你的信息执行器端点
see that one just works and we get that
看到一个只是工作，我们得到了
information coming back out and the the
信息回来了，
commit ID and if I look at a security
提交ID，如果我查看安全性
endpoint an endpoint like M it'll ask me
像M这样的端点会问我
for the details and I can log in with
有关详细信息，我可以使用
user magic and then I get my endpoint so
用户魔术，然后我得到了终点
this one is a example of an endpoint
这是端点的一个例子
that shows you kind of all the all
告诉你所有的一切
properties that you've got set I guess
我猜你已经设置的属性
worth taking a quick note here that this
值得在这里快速说明一下
this JSON data when we upgrade the
升级JSON数据时，
application you'll see that some of our
应用程序，您将看到我们的一些
formats have changed slightly for quite
格式略有变化
good reasons but but this one you can
有充分的理由，但是您可以
see at the moment we just have like that
看到此刻我们只有那样
the properties are kind of grouped by
属性按类型分组
property source and we just kind of dump
财产来源，我们只是某种形式的转储
everything out okay so hopefully that's
一切都很好，希望那是
clear so what I want to do now is take
清楚，所以我现在想做的是
this app and upgrade it so I'm gonna
这个程序并升级它，所以我要
stop it running I want to upgrade it to
停止运行我想升级到
spring route 2 to kind of show you the
春季路线2向您展示
processes that you'll have to go through
您必须经历的过程
so for most applications if you're not
因此对于大多数应用程序，如果您不是
doing kind of too much deep integration
做太多的深度整合
hopefully it's just a case of changing
希望这只是一个变化的情况
this version number so if you change the
这个版本号，所以如果您更改
parent version if we save that file and
父版本（如果我们保存该文件）和
look at our maven dependencies you'll
看看我们对Maven的依赖
see that's immediately upgraded both
看到这两个都立即升级
spring boot and all of the kind of
spring boot 和所有类型的
third-party dependencies so here we've
第三方依赖关系，所以我们在这里
got Tomcat 8 5 to 8 which is the major
得到了Tomcat 8 5到8这是主要的
system stable Tomcat we've got spring
系统稳定的Tomcat我们已经有了 Spring
MVC 5 and we've got spring boot - OH
MVC 5，我们已经有了 spring boot -哦
however we have got some compile time
但是我们有一些编译时间
issues so in this case the first thing
问题，所以在这种情况下，第一件事
that's broken is the data binder so I
数据绑定器坏了，所以我
said I pick something that was going to
说我选了一些东西
cause us some pain and in this case it's
给我们带来一些痛苦，在这种情况下
the relaxed data binder so relax data
放松的数据绑定器，所以放松数据
binder was a spring boot 1 5 class and
活页夹是一个 spring boot 1 5类和
it built on spring frameworks data
它基于Spring Framework 数据
binder which was really used for binding
真正用于绑定的活页夹
objects that come in over the web mainly
主要通过网络进入的对象
and we wanted to kind of move away from
我们想从
that and spring boot 2 and pick
那和 Spring 引导2然后选择
something that was kind of better suited
更适合的东西
for our purpose of binding to
为了我们绑定到
configuration properties so in spring
春季配置属性
boot - we have a new class and
引导-我们有一个新的班级，
called binder so what I need to do is
叫做活页夹，所以我需要做的是
make use of a new class called binder
利用称为活页夹的新类
and of course there were like a fails
当然会有失败
and binders in the class pass the one I
和班上的粘合剂通过了我
want is this and binder takes one or
想要的是，活页夹需要一个或
more configuration property sources so a
更多配置属性来源，因此
configuration property source is a
配置属性源是
special type of special type of source
特殊类型特殊类型来源
that the binder needs and you can either
粘合剂需要的，您可以
get a binder from the environment and we
从环境中获取粘合剂，我们
adapt all of the spring property sources
适应所有春季物业资源
that you have or you can create your own
拥有的或者您可以创建自己的
so I'm going to just make use of a map
所以我要利用地图
one which takes a map as a source and
一个以地图为源的
kind of presents it as something that
呈现为某种东西
this binder can use and for the source
这种粘合剂可以使用和作为来源
I'll just use the ammo that we had
我只会用我们拥有的弹药
earlier okay so that's our binder and if
早一点好吧，那是我们的粘合剂，如果
we want to bind we need to provide two
我们想绑定我们需要提供两个
things like there's a few overloaded
像是有些超载
versions but basically we need to
版本，但基本上我们需要
provide a name so in this case I want to
提供一个名字，所以在这种情况下我想
bind cities and then we need to provide
绑定城市，然后我们需要提供
a target and a target is some ultimately
一个目标，一个目标最终是一些
one of these bindable objects so
这些可绑定对象之一
bindable gives us a way to describe the
可绑定为我们提供了一种描述
thing that you want to bind it's much
你想绑定的东西很多
more flexible than having to have a real
比必须拥有一个真正的
instance of an object so we can actually
对象的实例，因此我们实际上可以
declare things like in this case I'm
在这种情况下声明我
going to want a list of a particular
想要一个特定的列表
class and we can give it annotations or
类，我们可以给它注解或
an existing value etc so I'm just going
现有价值等，所以我就去
to say I want a binder ball and I want a
说我想要一个活页夹球，我想要一个
list of cities so city dog grass and
城市清单，所以城市狗草和
that's about it I think this object
就是这个，我认为这个对象
actually returns something called a bind
实际返回的东西称为绑定
result so it doesn't return the bound
结果，所以它不返回界限
object directly it returns something
直接对象它返回一些东西
that returns the object so you can think
返回对象，以便您可以思考
of it a bit like optional and if you use
它有点像可选的，如果您使用
Java rate streams it's a bit like
Java速率流有点像
optional and you can see gives us a
可选，您可以看到给我们一个
bunch of methods that we can say did it
一堆我们可以说做到的方法
binds successfully we can do mapping
成功绑定，我们可以进行映射
functions too
也起作用
converted to something else the like or
转换为其他类似的东西或
else returns but I'm just going to do
否则返回，但我只是要做
get which you'll return it if it was
得到它，如果它是你会返回它
bound and thrown exception if it wasn't
如果不是，则抛出绑定异常
and that should be enough I think we no
那应该足够了，我认为我们没有
longer need this kind of crazy class
不再需要这种疯狂的课程
that describe just a list that can go
只描述一个可以去的清单
away and that's it we should be
走了，就是这样，我们应该
compiling again something imports out
再次编译一些东西导入
okay so people things about this binder
好的，所以人们对此粘合剂的看法
this binder currently we've got it to
这个活页夹目前我们已经到了
work with the way that configuration
使用配置方式
properties currently work but I said
物业目前可以使用，但我说过
this is a lot more flexible than in the
这比在
design so in the future we're going to
设计，以便将来我们将
try and support things like Kotlin data
尝试并支持Kotlin数据之类的东西
classes and possibly even have
类甚至可能有
interfaces that you can define
您可以定义的接口
properties in configuration properties
配置属性中的属性
of it kind of create some automatically
它会自动创建一些
without you needing to do quite so much
不需要做很多事情
getters and setters in your own code
您自己的代码中的获取器和设置器
okay so the surfacing runs okay so it
好的，这样铺面就可以了
seems to stuff up spring Roo to release
似乎塞满了 Spring Roo以释放
which is good let's go back over here
很好，让我们回到这里
and have a look our city's endpoint and
看看我们城市的终点
okay so the first thing that's kind of
好吧，第一件事就是
interesting here is we're being asked to
有趣的是，我们被要求
log in now whereas previously we weren't
现在登录，而以前我们没有
okay we'll login with our user magic
好吧，我们将使用我们的用户魔术登录
password and then you can see here we're
密码，然后您可以在此处看到我们
also getting like current rock in
也越来越像现在的摇滚
because the credentials about and if we
因为关于以及如果我们
go back to our console we can actually
回到控制台，我们实际上可以
see we've got we've got one of these
看到我们有其中之一
generated security passwords which is a
生成的安全密码是
little bit strange but okay let's try
有点奇怪，但是可以尝试
that hit the city seven point again okay
再打七分
so the apps kind of working we've got
因此应用程序可以正常工作
data coming back but clearly some things
数据返回，但显然有些事情
are a little bit off with it so let's
有点偏离，所以让我们
have a quick look back at the air and
快速回顾一下空气，
see what's going on
看看发生了什么
so with with spring boot - we've taken
所以用 spring boot -我们采取了
the opportunity to kind of rationalize a
有机会合理化的机会
lot of the properties so we have quite a
很多属性，所以我们有一个
lot of properties that you could set and
您可以设置的许多属性
he tended to pick a lot of top-level
他倾向于选择很多顶级人才
names for them which kind of made things
给他们起什么样的名字
a little bit confusing so what we've
有点令人困惑，所以我们已经
actually done we just update this to get
实际完成后，我们只需更新此内容即可
rid of that error what we've done in
摆脱了我们所做的错误
boot 2 is taken a chance to kind of
引导2借此机会
rename a few of them and if you open
重命名其中一些，如果您打开
your application properties and if
您的应用程序属性以及
you've got an IDE that supports spring
您有一个支持spring的IDE
boots property metadata you should see
引导您应该看到的属性元数据
kind of you get some errors so in this
有点像你这样的错误
case we've got like a couple of problems
情况我们有几个问题
here the security dot basic enabled is
这里启用的安全点基本是
telling me that security is no longer
告诉我安全不再
customizable so that one's gone ok we'll
可定制的，这样我们就可以了
come back to that and the the user
回到那个和用户
password is deprecated and it's telling
密码已弃用，这说明
me that there's a different one to use
我有另一种使用
instead so we could obviously just fix
相反，我们显然可以解决
these up like it's pretty easy that just
这些就好像很容易
change these in the file but if you've
在文件中更改这些，但是如果您已经
got like a B app or if you're not using
像B应用程序，或者如果您不使用
an ID that's kind of giving you this
一个可以给你这个的ID
information you might want to kind of
您可能想要的信息
take a more gradual approach so to help
采取更渐进的方法，以便提供帮助
out with that there's a new dependency
有了新的依赖
that you can add to your project so I'm
您可以将其添加到您的项目中，以便
just going to add that in there
只是要在那里添加
so spring root property properties
所以Spring 根属性
migrator is a little additional
迁移器是额外的
dependency that you can throw into your
你可以扔进你的依赖
project and if we run this application
项目，如果我们运行此应用程序
again without fixing those errors this
再次没有解决这些错误
time you'll see a couple of things
时间，你会看到几件事
interesting happened first of all bigger
有趣的事情首先更大
we don't get a generated password so
我们没有生成密码，所以
it's kind of fixed it but we are getting
这是固定的，但我们越来越
a couple of these warnings so we are
这些警告中的一些，所以我们是
getting something locked out saying this
拒绝说些什么
property source it's telling us exactly
财产来源告诉我们确切
which file it's in and then this key and
它在哪个文件中，然后此键和
the line number that that key is on has
该键所在的行号
been replaced with this value so it's
被替换为该值，因此
telling us not
告诉我们不要
only that this has changed but because
只是这已经改变了，但是因为
this migrate has got some smarts about
这种迁移有一些聪明之处
it it's able to migrate for us so for
它能够为我们迁移，因此
now it's changed dynamically change this
现在它已经动态更改了
to this until we've have a chance to fix
为此，直到我们有机会修复
it and then it's also telling us about
它然后还告诉我们有关
the other one that's gone away they
另一个已经消失的人
obviously can't do much about that so
显然不能为此做太多事情
could you show us the yellow file real
你能告诉我们黄色的文件吗
quick yeah sure awesome so the amyl on
快速是的，肯定很棒，所以上了戊基
the M was kind of on a pretty
M有点漂亮
straightforward let me bring it side by
坦率的让我来带它
side with the binder just to show you
与粘合剂的一面只是为了向您展示
the kind of logic that you've got so
你所拥有的那种逻辑
that the ammo is just like a one key in
弹药就像一把钥匙
a list of elements with the name country
名称为country的元素列表
name country name country so the way
命名国家命名国家
that the binder works is this properties
粘结剂起作用的就是这个特性
object here we'll end up with elements
对象在这里，我们将最终获得元素
that look like this
看起来像这样
like it'll have City dots sorry city
希望它有城市点对不起城市
cities naught dot name equals cities
零点名称等于城市
naught dot country calls and then like
零点乡村电话，然后喜欢
one etc etc so so that Yammer gets
一个等等等等，以便Yammer得到
actually flatten out into a property
实际上变成一个财产
structure and then the binder basically
结构然后是粘合剂
says okay I want a list of cities so
说好吧，我想要一个城市清单，所以
that kind of maps to the list
那种映射到列表
yeah Mille and then if you look at the
是的Mille然后如果你看
city there setters for that name sir
那个名字的城市有二传手
country so those the binder basically
国家，所以那些活页夹基本上
will create one city for each element of
将为的每个元素创建一个城市
the list then call set name set country
列表然后呼叫设置名称设置国家
etc alright Lex
等等Lex
appreciate it thank you all right I want
感谢它，谢谢，我想要
to highlight something else that's kind
突出一些其他的善意
of coming nice about this it's migrator
很好地解决了这个问题
thing which is a new feature that is
这是一个新功能
kind of subtle but you'll see it used
有点微妙，但您会看到它的使用
quite in quite a few places and boot to
在很多地方都可以启动
this line number stuff is something
这个行号的东西是东西
called origin
被称为起源
so in boot we have this new interface
所以在启动时我们有了这个新界面
called
叫
origin and it's pretty dumb in fact it
起源，而且实际上很愚蠢
doesn't really do anything other than
除了做其他事情
say it's got a two string that
说它有两个字符串
implements something sensible and then
实施明智的做法，然后
we have some subclasses of it so we have
我们有一些子类，所以我们有
text resource origin for example tell
文本资源来源例如tell
you the resource and like location which
您的资源和喜欢的位置
is the line on column number and various
是列号上的行和各种
other ones but every time we load a file
其他的，但是每次加载文件时
now a llaman file or a properties file
现在是llaman文件或属性文件
we're able to track precisely where a
我们能够精确跟踪
particular value is coming from so this
特殊的价值来自于此
origin gets used in a few places we'll
我们将在几个地方使用起源
see it later when we look at the
稍后再看
actuator end point if you've got like
执行器终点，如果您喜欢
validation errors then we often show the
验证错误，那么我们通常会显示
origin as like you know to say like this
像你这样说的起源
string is empty and the values that I
字符串为空，我的值
found it in is in this file this this
在此文件中找到它
line and column number so we think this
行号和列号，所以我们认为
kind of feature is actually going to be
实际上是一种功能
quite useful
很有用
okay so let's fix up these things so
好吧，让我们修复这些问题，以便
that one can just go away and this one
那一个人就可以走了，这个
needs to change to spring got security
需要改变以确保安全
dot user password equals magic okay
点用户密码等于不可思议
because we've migrated these as well
因为我们也已经迁移了这些
this this property migrator thing you
这是这个财产移民的事
know it doesn't come for free it's got
知道它不是免费的，它有
to do some logic it's gotta look through
做一些逻辑，它必须通过
we properties and kind of work out if
我们的属性和工作方式，如果
you'll use any deprecated ones so once
您将使用所有已弃用的设备，因此一次
you're kind of happy and you've migrated
你很高兴，你已经迁移了
it's best to remove it so it's not kind
最好将其删除，所以它不是一种
of doing any extra work so I'm just
做任何额外的工作，所以我只是
going to get rid of it again all right
要再次摆脱它好吧
so let's just check this thing still
所以我们还是检查一下
works yeah so we start up we've not got
是的，所以我们开始我们还没有
the generated password which is good but
生成的密码很好，但是
what I want to do is I want to fix this
我想做的是要解决此问题
clear that's a sec I want to fix the
清楚，这是我想修复的几秒钟
fact that two seconds
事实上，两秒钟
so I want to fix the fact that is asking
所以我想解决这个问题
for this login because in the old
对于此登录，因为在旧
version like cities and city were open
像城市和城市这样的版本是开放的
and I want to make that the same with
我想用
the new version now in spring but--one
现在是春季的新版本，但是-一个
five kind of security configuration we
我们的五种安全配置
we tried to do but we try to do quite a
我们试图做，但我们尝试做一个相当
lot for you so we tried to kind of split
很适合您，因此我们尝试了一些拆分
the configuration and say ok that's
配置，然后说确定
actuator we'll configure that for you
执行器，我们将为您配置
but you can do your own configuration
但您可以自己配置
and you have to order things to get them
你必须订购东西才能得到它们
in the right the right place so that
在正确的地方
ours would run before after yours and it
我们的会在你的之后
it kind of worked but it would quickly
这种工作，但很快
get confusing so in boot - we've decided
在启动时会感到困惑-我们已经决定
that we're just going to do away with
我们将要消除
all that and we effectively if you have
所有这些，如果您有，我们将有效
security on the classpath we consider
我们考虑的类路径上的安全性
that to be a signal that you want to do
这是你想做的信号
enable web security in exactly the same
完全相同地启用网络安全
way as you would if you were just doing
就像您只是在做一样
spring security manually and if you want
Spring 安全手动，如果你想
to kind of configure things then it's
进行某种配置，然后
down to you and you're going to have to
取决于你，你将不得不
create your own security configuration
创建自己的安全配置
so I'm going to create a new class
所以我要开一个新班
called security configuration and I'm
称为安全配置，我
gonna make it a configuration no not
要做一个配置
conditional a configuration and I'm
有条件的配置，我
gonna make use of Springs web security
将利用Springs网络安全
configure adapter so spring Security's
配置适配器，以便Spring Security的
web skipping web security configure
网页跳过网页安全配置
adapter okay
适配器好
so this is the way you kind of
所以这就是你的方式
traditionally to you know set up your
传统上，您知道设置您的
spring security configuration and the
Spring 安全配置和
way I personally like to do this kind of
我个人喜欢做这种方式
stuff is I like to just have one of
我喜欢只拥有其中之一
these because I find that you know
这些，因为我发现你知道
difficult enough to setup security
难以设置安全性
without having things kind of spread
没有东西传播
across multiple classes so what we've
跨多个类，所以我们已经
tried to do in boot 2 is give you kind
试图在引导2中做的就是给你一种
of helper classes that you can use when
您可以在何时使用的辅助类
you just want to have a single security
您只想拥有一个证券
configuration so I need to configure my
配置，所以我需要配置我的
HTTP security and I want to change it so
HTTP安全性，我想更改它
that my actuator endpoints are open now
我的执行器端点现已打开
a couple of tips if you look at the
一些技巧，如果你看
superclass of this one you'll see this
这个的超类，你会看到这个
is what spring security does by default
默认情况下是spring security所做的
and just kind of helpful so I'm going to
有点帮助，所以我要
take that I'm going to use that as a
认为我将使用它作为一个
kind of basis of mine now what I want to
我现在想要的一种基础
do is I want to say I need a request
我想说我需要一个请求
that's going to my any actuator endpoint
这将是我执行器的任何终点
I want to say you need to be logged in
我想说你需要登录
and any other web endpoint I'm just not
和其他任何网络端点
bothered about so you can just access it
麻烦了，所以你就可以访问它
so I need to somehow have something that
所以我需要某种方式
matches against the the actuator
与执行器匹配
endpoint and spring Security's got this
端点和Spring Security得到了这个
request matches method that takes a
请求匹配方法需要一个
request matcher so in spring Boop what
请求匹配器，所以在春季Boop
we've done is rather than like trying to
我们所做的不是喜欢尝试
give you multiple configurations we give
给您我们提供的多种配置
you this endpoint request object
您这个端点请求对象
endpoint request so there's two versions
端点请求，所以有两个版本
the one I want is the servlet one an
我想要的是servlet一个
endpoint request gives you a quick way
端点请求为您提供了一种快速的方法
to build up matches that match actuator
建立匹配致动器的匹配
endpoints so in this case I want to say
端点，所以在这种情况下，我想说
if you're going to any of my actuator
如果你要去我的执行器
endpoints then I'm going to make you
终结点，然后我会让你
authenticated and if you're going to
通过身份验证，如果您要
can't spell and if you go into any
不能拼写，如果你遇到任何
request then I'm going to say permit all
请求，然后我要说允许所有
for this one so I've changed this ring
为了这个，我换了这枚戒指
security defaults and say permit all and
安全默认值，并说允许所有和
then I'll carry on with form locket
然后我继续用小盒坠子
login and HTTP basic so it's just a bit
登录和HTTP基本功能，仅需一点点
easier to read organize reverse ok so
更容易阅读整理反向，所以
let's see does this work
让我们看看这项工作
so I'm going back to cities so there we
所以我要回城市，在那里
go you can see this time our city's
去，你可以看到这次我们的城市
endpoint works let's have a look at
端点工作原理让我们看一下
London again that one works and let us
伦敦再次证明了这一点，让我们
hit our info actuator endpoint see if
击中我们的信息执行器端点，看是否
that one works and we have got an error
那个工作，我们有一个错误
here so we're not getting a security
在这里，所以我们没有安全保障
exception we're getting a 404 which is
例外，我们得到的是404
saying this this endpoint isn't found
说找不到此端点
which is interesting and the reason the
这很有趣，原因是
same point isn't found is because we've
找不到同一点是因为我们已经
moved them all so again in boot 1/5 we
再次在引导1/5中移动了它们，我们
kind of discovered our mistake a bit too
有点发现我们的错误
late but all of the actuator endpoints
迟到但所有执行器端点
kind of sat off the root so you could do
有点脱离根，所以你可以做
info or mbeans and it worked kind of
信息或mbeans，它的工作原理是
fine but there was a those a few
很好，但是有一些
problems with it one it was kind of hard
问题之一，这很难
to secure he kind of these things would
确保他有这些东西会
sneak in and you weren't sure and two it
偷偷溜进去，你不确定和两个
became very hard for us you know as
对我们来说变得非常困难，你知道
developers a spring boot to add
开发人员添加一个 spring boot
additional endpoints that we might need
我们可能需要的其他端点
without worrying that they might clash
不用担心他们可能会发生冲突
with endpoints that you've already
与您已经拥有的端点
defined so in order to fix that in in
定义以便将其修复
boot - we've moved them all so they're
靴子-我们已将它们全部移走，因此它们
all now under actuator so if I hit
现在都在执行器下，所以如果我打
actuator slash info I'm getting the log
执行器斜线信息我正在获取日志
in because that matches our security
因为这符合我们的安全性
configuration and if I log in then we
配置，如果我登录，那么我们
get we're getting that information back
得到我们正在获取该信息
out again so that the the info endpoint
再次退出，以便信息端点
is now working let's have a quick check
现在正在工作，让我们快速检查一下
of em as well and ok interestingly M is
以及em的值，有趣的是M是
still not there why is that well if we
还是不在那里，如果我们为什么那么好
look at actuator we get a list of all
看看执行器，我们得到所有的清单
the endpoints that we've got set up so
我们已经建立的端点
this is a Hal formatted JSON structure
这是Hal格式的JSON结构
and you can do this in in boot 1/5 but
并且您可以在启动1/5中执行此操作，但是
you have to add a dependency on spring
您必须添加对spring的依赖
hey Geoff's and you have to set up this
嘿，杰夫，你必须设置这个
actuator path yourself and it's bring
执行器路径自己带来
boots - you don't need to do that it's
靴子-您不需要这样做
all kind of done for you and it
为您做的所有事情
the box even if you don't have the extra
即使你没有多余的东西
dependency and you can see here that
依赖性，您可以在此处看到
we've got like three we've got the
我们已经三岁了
actuator one health and info and we're
执行器一个健康和信息，我们
missing like a whole ton and the reason
像一吨一样失踪，原因
we're missing those is because you've
我们想念那些是因为你已经
decided to switch them off by default so
决定默认情况下将其关闭
so that you don't accidentally expose
这样您才不会意外暴露
information that you didn't want to so
您不想这样的信息
if we want to enable them again what we
如果我们想再次启用它们，我们
need to do is we need to add a property
需要做的是我们需要添加一个属性
so Fitness property that we want to AB
所以我们要健身的财产AB
is management dot and points yeah sorry
是管理点和点，对不起
this one so management or endpoints that
因此，管理层或端点
web got exposure and then you can see
网络曝光，然后您可以看到
there's two you can have an include and
有两个可以包含一个
exclude set so I'm going to change the
排除设置，所以我要更改
include one to star which is just going
包括一个即将开始的明星
to enable everything so you can you can
启用所有功能，以便您可以
see how you can easily have like an
看看您如何轻松拥有像
included star and exclude of like beans
包括星号，不包括类似beans
so you want everything except beans or
所以你想要除beans或beans以外的所有东西
if you want to be like more precise you
如果你想变得更精确
can just list the ones that you want to
可以只列出您想要的
include and not worry about the exclude
包含而不担心排除
ones let's just restart again and if I
那些让我们再次重新启动，如果我
hit actuated now you can see we have
打动现在你可以看到我们有
like all of our end points back again
像我们所有的终点一样
which is good and let's have a quick
很好，让我们快速
look at the end end point so while
看完终点
you're doing that I just want to say
你这样做我只是想说
that Philco will be available after the
Philco将在
session a number of people have been
会议上已有很多人
asking and we'll address your questions
问，我们将解决您的问题
at the end thank you yeah if there's
最后谢谢你，如果有
anything that's not player Peter shell
任何不是玩家Peter Shell的东西
so I can like if there's a thing that's
所以我想如果有什么事情是
people are confused about shout and I'll
人们对喊叫感到困惑，我会
try and address it as we go but
尝试解决这个问题，但是
otherwise we'll do them all at the end
否则我们会在最后全部完成
right so this is the mmm point and you
对，所以这是mmm点，您
can I want to point out the JSON is
我想指出JSON是
slightly different here so we've we've
略有不同，所以我们已经
taken a chance to kind of organize our
借此机会组织了我们的
jason in a much more kind of sane way so
杰森以一种更加理智的方式
here
这里
we have property sources are listed as a
我们将物业来源列为
list which is nice and we also have this
列表很好，我们也有这个
origin stuff again so like if you look
原来的东西又像你看
at any particular property like in photo
在任何特定的属性（例如照片）中
app name you can see the value and where
您可以查看应用名称的值以及位置
it came from so is saying I came from
它来自说我来自
this class math resource right down to
此类数学资源
the line and column number that it was
行号和列号
declared at and you can also dig into an
在声明，您还可以挖掘一个
individual value which is nice so I
个人价值很好，所以我
could say hey where did this particular
可以说嘿，这个特殊的地方在哪里
value come from what did you do to find
价值来自您所做的发现
it and it's going to tell me okay it's
它会告诉我好吧
the value is this and this is where I
就是这个，这就是我的所在
got it from but also these are all the
从那里得到的，但这些都是
property sources that I tried along the
我尝试过的资源来源
way so I tried all of these and they
方式，所以我尝试了所有这些，他们
didn't have it so if you have with
没有，所以如果你有
spring move it's easy to override
Spring 移动，很容易覆盖
properties so you can override like an
属性，因此您可以像
environment variable for instance you
例如您的环境变量
can have something in your properties
可以在你的财产中有东西
file and you declare an environment
文件，然后声明环境
variable that changes it and that's nice
改变它的变量，这很好
but sometimes it can be a little bit
但有时可能会有点
like confusing as to where did this
喜欢混淆在哪里
thing actually come from so this little
东西实际上来自这么少
end point gives you a nice way to kind
终点给您一种很好的友善方式
of find that out I can see all the bonds
的发现，我可以看到所有的债券
are tied the fact they didn't return
绑着他们没有回来的事实
anything and then the one that did is my
任何事情，然后做的是我的
application properties form I think we
应用程序属性表，我认为我们
have like a fully working application
像一个完全正常的应用程序
again let me see if there's anything
再次让我看看是否有什么
else I want to show you before moving
否则我想在移动之前告诉你
off from that let's let's go ahead and
从那开始，让我们继续前进，
migrate this now to make it a little bit
现在迁移它，使其有点
more reactive so I'm going to take what
反应性更强，所以我要采取什么
we've done and I'm going to migrate it
我们已经完成了，我将要迁移它
to a reactive application but before I
到反应性应用程序，但在我之前
do that I want to just show you some
我只是想给你看一些
something interesting that I think is
我觉得很有趣
worth kind of discussing when we come on
值得讨论，我们什么时候来
to the later section so I'm going to add
到下一节，所以我要添加
a couple of breakpoints I've got my city
我有我的城市的几个断点
controller and I've added a breakpoint
控制器，我添加了一个断点
on the all method
在所有方法上
and I've got my city class and I've
我上了城市课，
added a breakpoint on getname can let's
在getname上添加一个断点可以让我们
start this up again in debug mode okay
再次以调试模式启动它
and then I'm going to hit my city's
然后我要去我城市的
endpoint and show you what's going on so
端点并向您显示发生了什么
what I want you to look at is the
我要你看的是
threads so threads in a spring do
线程，所以Spring 中的线程会
blocking application you can see we have
阻止应用程序，您可以看到我们有
more than fit on my page and the
远远超过我的页面和
majority of them of these HTTP nio 8080
其中大多数HTTPniño8080
ones so these are threads that Tomcat
这些是Tomcat的线程
has created and if we look at the way
已经创造了，如果我们看看方式
this application is currently working
这个应用程式目前正在运作
you can see that my city controller is
你可以看到我的城市管理员是
hit and it's using exec one thread and
命中，它正在使用执行一个线程，
if I just carry on running now my all
如果我现在继续跑步
method is still on exec one and may get
该方法仍然在执行程序一上并且可能会得到
named methods are being called also on
命名方法也被调用
exec one so you can see get name get
执行一个，所以你可以看到获得名称
name get name get name get name and then
名称获取名称获取名称获取名称，然后
our data gets back again so that thread
我们的数据再次返回，以便该线程
this this exact one thread in this case
在这种情况下，这正是一个线程
the tomcat thread is handling um that
tomcat线程正在处理um
request from start to finish
从头到尾的要求
okay let's migrate this app gradually to
好吧，让我们逐步将这个应用程序迁移到
reactive I'm going to start by just
反应性我将从一开始就开始
migrating the date a bit so spring MVC
迁移日期有点 Spring MVC
will support reactive return types and
支持无功回报类型和
do its best to kind of deal with them
尽力与他们打交道
for you which means we can do this like
对您来说，这意味着我们可以做到
conversion in two parts the first part
分为两部分，第一部分
I'm going to do is the data so I want to
我要做的是数据，所以我想
change MongoDB and I want to change it
更改MongoDB，我想更改它
to a reactive application so all of the
到反应性应用程序，因此所有
starters that we've got in spring boot
我们在 spring boot 中获得的入门
for the data starters if there is
对于数据入门者（如果有）
reactive support available then there's
可用的反应性支持，然后有
a reactive equivalent so I just need to
无功等效，所以我只需要
change this starter to spring boot
将此启动器更改为Spring Boot
starter data MongoDB reactive
入门数据MongoDB反应式
and if I save this application here and
如果我在这里保存该应用程序，
look at the dependencies the one that I
看看我的依赖
want to show you hopefully it reactive
希望向您展示它的反应性
streets yet so we have a reactive
街道，所以我们有一个反应
streams import that's now coming in and
流导入现在正在进入
somewhere in this list is project
此列表中的某处是项目
reactor as well which is a way that we
反应堆也是我们的一种方式
like to kind of work with reactive
喜欢以被动的方式工作
applications so I'm now I'm going to
应用程序，所以我现在要去
change my repository to make use of
更改我的存储库以利用
these new data types my my repository at
这些新数据类型位于我的存储库中
the moment has got these two methods and
当下有这两种方法
if I return if I call find all and
如果我打电话回去，找到所有
basically this comes back as a fully
基本上这回来了
populated list or ready to roll and if I
填充列表或准备滚动，如果我
call find by naming all in case I get
通过命名所有内容来呼叫查找，以防万一
like a single one again right completely
像一个人一样完全对
ready and what I want to do is I no
准备好了，我想做的是我不
longer want to return the thing I want
不再想归还我想要的东西
to return something that will provide
返回将提供的东西
the thing when it's ready so I want I
东西准备好了，所以我想要我
want to be non-blocking if I can call
希望我可以打电话给我
find all I want to get something back
找到所有我想找回的东西
immediately and that's something I want
立即，那是我想要的
to be able to listen to and it will tell
能够听，它会告诉
me when the data is available so I want
我什么时候有数据，所以我想要
to change this one to something called a
将此更改为一种称为
flux and I want to change this one to
流量，我想将其更改为
something cause I'm mono
因为我单身
okay so what a flux our motto looks and
好吧，我们的座右铭看起来和
mono are both implementations of this
单声道都是这个的实现
thing called a publisher so this is a
叫做发布者的东西，所以这是一个
reactive streams specification so this
反应流规格因此
is like a consortium that came together
就像一个聚在一起的财团
and try to work out a way of getting
并设法找到一种获取
reactive applications to to be
反应性应用
interoperable with each other and it's
彼此可互操作，并且
pretty simple like interface here you
很简单，就像这里的界面
can just subscribe to it and it will
可以订阅它，它将
tell you basically when data is
基本上告诉您数据何时
available or if there's been an error
可用或有错误
reactor kind of so this is a reactive
反应堆类型，所以这是反应性的
streams type these are project reactor
流类型，这些是项目反应堆
types they're they're kind of helpful
他们是他们的类型，他们很有帮助
implementations and a mono is something
实现和单声道是东西
that represents kind of zero or one
代表零或一
results and the flux represents the kind
结果和通量代表那种
of stream of results potentially kind of
结果流的种类
infinite so you can see like this is
无限，所以您可以看到这样的
going to return more than one city and
要返回一个以上的城市，
this is going to return just a single
这将只返回一个
city or no city at all okay well we kind
一个城市或根本没有一个城市好吧，我们好
of okay but we've broken our city
可以，但是我们已经打破了城市
controller now so what we need to do
控制器，所以我们需要做的
here is change our city controller to
这是将我们的城市管理员更改为
actually return the appropriate types as
实际上返回适当的类型为
well I said spring MVC you can kind of
我说过春季MVC，您可以
deal with them so I want to return a
与他们打交道，所以我想退货
flux from this one and I want to return
来自这一方面的变化，我想返回
a mono from this one and we're almost
这个单声道，我们差不多
working except we don't have this stream
工作，除了我们没有这个流
function on flux so findall is returning
对通量起作用，因此findall返回
a flux and not a list so we don't have
流量而不是列表，所以我们没有
streams now the goodness is that why
流的好处是，为什么
you'd want to use these flocks and
你想用这些羊群和
monotypes is they have like a whole
单型是他们像一个整体
bunch of kind of useful operations that
一堆有用的操作
you can do on them so this this guy is a
你可以对他们做，所以这个家伙是一个
really nice programming model it's very
非常好的编程模型，它非常
similar to the kind streams API but much
与同类流API相似，但很多
more rich so I can just get rid of
更富有，所以我可以摆脱
stream
流
because there's a filter method that we
因为我们有一种过滤方法
can use directly and I no longer need to
可以直接使用，我不再需要
collect it because I just returning the
收集它，因为我刚返回
flux anyway so that's our new code so
无论如何，所以这是我们的新代码
again like this is saying final all
再次像这样说最终
their things filter it for the USA and
他们的东西过滤了美国和
return that straight out as a flux
直接将其作为通量返回
immediately and let spring MVC deal with
立即让Spring MVC处理
it okay see if that if that works
好的，看看是否可行
no why not okay occasionally for some
不，为什么有时候不行
unknown reason embedded Mongo goes wrong
未知原因嵌入式Mongo出问题
so when I was doing this earlier it was
所以当我早些时候做的是
falling over it seems like if you just
跌倒好像你只是
run it again it's happy okay if you see
再次运行它，如果看到就很高兴
me restart the app because of an arrow
我因为箭头而重新启动了应用程序
it's because embedded Mongo has got
这是因为嵌入式Mongo有
himself in a bit of a teaser all right
自己有点挑逗
so that's we have this okay so we're
所以这就是我们可以的，所以我们
working again have a quick look at
再次工作快速浏览
what's going on we have see all that we
发生了什么，我们已经看到了所有
still have all these threads in fact we
实际上所有这些线程仍然存在
have slightly more threads now and
现在有更多的线程，
something interesting is going to happen
有趣的事情将会发生
the first hit that we've got here where
我们来到这里的第一击
we're on what I missed it yes sorry I
我们在我错过的事情上，是的，对不起，我
missed it let me do that again
错过了，让我再做一次
nice to lose the breakpoint okay
很高兴失去断点好吗
refresh so the first hit here while
刷新，所以第一次点击这里
we're doing this the city controller
我们正在做这个城市管理员
method you can see this time we're in
这次我们可以看到的方法
tomcat thread 3 okay if I carry on the
tomcat线程3好吧，如果我继续
getname method is in thread 4 so unlike
getname方法在线程4中，因此与
the first application where everything
第一个应用程序在哪里
kind of happened in the same thread
发生在同一线程中
we're doing like a thread jump here and
我们就像在这里跳线一样
the reason for that is that spring MVC
原因是 Spring 的MVC
is doing its best to deal with these
正在尽最大努力应对这些
reactive types and it's using servlets
反应性类型，它正在使用servlet
async supports so it's doing a start I
异步支持，所以它正在做一个开始
think when it returns the first data and
想一想它何时返回第一个数据并
then the actual processing is being
那么实际的处理是
handled in a later other thread so it's
在以后的其他线程中处理，因此
basically doing the best it can to make
基本上是尽力而为
this application a reactive application
此应用程序为响应式应用程序
but we are not like fully reactive at
但是我们不喜欢在
this point so I say spring MVC is doing
这一点，所以我说Spring MVC正在做
its best but what we really want to do
最好，但我们真正想做的是
is switch to a completely non blocking
切换到完全非阻塞
server so I'm going to change my spring
服务器，所以我要改变我的 Spring
boot start a web to something else I'm
引导启动网站到我的其他地方
going to use spring Roo starter web
即将使用Spring Roo入门网站
plugs it was our question Peters no no
塞住这是我们的问题彼得斯否否
it's just it's interesting actually
其实很有趣
hearing from Ross and lately on how many
听到罗斯的消息，最近又听到了多少
customers have been actually quite
客户实际上已经相当
interested in the incremental move to
对逐步迁移到
reactive that that we can offer on in
我们可以提供的反应性
fact I have a blog that talks a little
事实上，我有一个谈论一些话题的博客
bit more about that from some of Ross's
罗斯的一些内容
comments that I'll talk about at the end
我将在最后讨论的评论
but I'm really happy you're showing this
但我很高兴你能展示这个
thanks because I think a lot of the
谢谢，因为我认为很多
existing spring MVC customers are you
现有的Spring MVC客户是您
know kind of curious about how do you
知道你如何好奇
sort of edge towards reactive rather
在反应性方面有点优势
than just jump in with both feet
不仅仅是双脚跳
so I think it's really great showed that
所以我认为这真的很棒
thank you ok cool there's a little bit
谢谢，好的，很酷
later if we get to it there's we've got
以后，如果我们能做到的话
some load testing that we do and we make
我们做的一些负载测试
use of a classical web plant which is in
使用经典的Web植物
the framework which is like a really
真正的框架
nice way of doing
做事的好方法
remote rest calls so I think a lot of
远程休息电话，所以我认为很多
people might start without it's kind of
人们可能会开始没有它的那种
a nice way to get your feet wet with
一个让你的脚湿透的好方法
with these reactive types without
这些反应类型没有
necessarily even converting your app to
甚至将您的应用程序转换为
a kind of fully reactive style see
一种完全反应的风格，请参见
exactly exactly your web client for the
正是您的网络客户端
wind yep
是的
all right so I think what we're done I
好的，我想我们做了什么
changed this dependency I've saved it
更改了此依赖关系，我已经保存了
IDs updated let's have a look at my
ID已更新，让我们看看我的
dependencies here and let's search for
依赖关系，让我们搜索
Tomcat and you'll see we don't have
Tomcat，您会看到我们没有
Tomcats let's search for servlet and you
Tomcats让我们搜索servlet，然后您
don't have servlets and they let's
没有servlet，而我们
search for Nettie and we do have Nettie
搜索Nettie，我们有Nettie
so in spring boot to the default server
所以在 spring boot 到默​​认服务器
that we give you if you want a web flex
如果您需要网络伸缩，我们会给您
application is Nettie and you still
应用程序是Nettie，您仍然
welcome to kind of switch that out and
欢迎采用那种切换
use some Tomcat but we don't work with
使用一些Tomcat，但我们无法使用
the servlet API so when you're doing a
servlet API，因此当您执行
web plugs application so you don't
网络插件应用程序，因此您不必
actually need the server api's if you're
实际需要服务器api
if you're doing a kind of web plugs app
如果您正在做一种网络插件应用
application you shouldn't interact with
您不应与之互动的应用程序
them they're the way that Tomcat works
它们是Tomcat工作的方式
is we have this kind of small bridge
我们有这种小桥吗
that fits on top of it okay
放在上面就可以了
seems to be working let's see if our app
似乎正在工作，让我们看看我们的应用程序
actually runs just curious Phil while
实际上运行只是好奇的菲尔
we're waiting is uh the the incremental
我们正在等待的是增量
switch you know is that also available
开关，您知道这也可用
with Jersey web client is uh has that
与泽西网络客户端是吗
work is that the searches um no depends
工作是搜索不依赖
on what you're doing like if you can't
如果你做不到的话
return as far as I'm aware you can't
据我所知你不能返回
return reactive types from a Jersey
从Jersey返回反应类型
resource oh um but you can still use
资源哦，但是您仍然可以使用
like web client within your Jersey code
就像您的Jersey代码中的网络客户端
if you would like if you have a if you
如果您愿意的话
were handling something that needs to go
正在处理需要去的东西
and do remote calls itself so it you
并自己进行远程呼叫
could still use reactive types but you
仍然可以使用反应类型，但是你
can't return them
无法退还他们
way that MVC can deal with them okay
MVC可以对付他们的方式
that's what I thought it wasn't quite
那就是我的想法
the same parish right thank you so much
同样的教区权利非常感谢你
now we've got a problem here so our
现在我们这里有一个问题，所以我们
applications although it's compiling
尽管正在编译的应用程序
it's like falling in a big heap because
就像掉进了一大堆，因为
the security configuration is somehow
安全配置是某种方式
using a servlet type and that makes kind
使用servlet类型，这使种类
of sense because the this kind of design
是因为这种设计
is this
这是
this adapter thing actually has always
这个适配器的东西实际上总是
used servlet types so in order to
使用了servlet类型，以便
migrate this application to a fully
将此应用迁移到完全
reactive app where we don't have these
没有这些的反应式应用程序
server types we can't use the same web
服务器类型，我们不能使用同一网站
security configurated app that we need
我们需要的安全配置的应用程序
to kind of change this class to
将该类更改为
something else so I need to replace the
其他的东西，所以我需要更换
security configuration with something
安全配置
else and in this case I just don't need
否则在这种情况下我就不需要
the adapter at all I need to return
我需要退货的适配器
something from a bean so I'm going to
beans里的东西，所以我要
change this to a be method public method
将其更改为be方法public方法
and I'm going to return a new spring
我要返回一个新的 Spring
security type called security web filter
安全类型称为安全Web筛选器
chain okay and let's make this a rename
好的，让我们重新命名
that method as well because it's now
该方法也是如此，因为现在
being has come something sensible okay
出现了明智的事
and I need to change this from HTTP
我需要从HTTP更改它
security to serve HTTP security so these
服务HTTP安全的安全性
are like reactive equivalents of the
就像
spring security types authorize requests
Spring Security 类型授权请求
no longer exists so I need to change
不再存在，所以我需要改变
that to something else it's actually
那实际上是
authorized exchange now requests matches
现在授权交易要求匹配
just no longer called the quest matches
只是不再称为任务比赛
it's called matches I think all matcher
我认为所有比赛者都称为比赛
matches this type here I said there was
匹配这种类型，我说有
two equivalents so I'm using the servlet
两个等效项，所以我正在使用servlet
one I need to chase out to the reactive
我需要向反应堆追逐
one and the API is the same but it
一个和API是相同的，但它
returns
退货
one of these the these matches now take
这些比赛之一，现在采取
us server web exchange matches so
美国服务器网络交换匹配
they're kind of similar but just a
他们有点相似，但只是
different API that doesn't use servlet
不使用servlet的不同API
types so that looks good this is not a
类型，以便看起来不错，这不是
request anymore it's an exchange and the
要求了，这是一次交流，
rest remains except I need to return
剩下的除了我需要返回
something so what I actually returned is
所以我实际上返回的是
the result of this and build okay
结果，并建立好
hopefully that's right let's give it a
希望是对的，让我们给它一个
go
走
that's just my embedded Mongo going
那只是我嵌入的Mongo
wrong again all right these work please
再次错了好吗这些工作请
work there we go so this is now a
我们去那里工作，所以现在
reactive application and it's doing
反应性应用程序，它正在做
exactly the same thing so let's some
完全一样的东西，让我们来一些
interesting points first of all we
有趣的一点首先我们
didn't need to actually change the city
并不需要真正改变城市
controller at all once it was returning
控制器一旦返回
these reactive types so a lot of people
这些反应性类型很多人
don't realize that the rest controller
没意识到剩下的控制器
annotations and the mapping annotations
注释和映射注释
like get mapping etc these are all part
像获取映射等这些都是
of a library called spring a web I think
我认为图书馆称为spring a web
it'll check yeah so they're part of
会检查的，所以他们是
spring web so they're not actually part
Spring Web，因此它们实际上不是一部分
of spring MVC and spring web flux makes
Spring MVC和Spring 腹板通量的变化
use of exactly the same annotations so
使用完全相同的注释
you can you can use exactly the same
你可以用完全一样的
kind of code and things just work the
某种代码，事情就可以了
only thing you need to be careful of is
您唯一需要注意的是
that you return types that are either
您返回的类型是
like immediately available or are
喜欢立即可用或
reactive types so that you don't block
反应类型，这样您就不会阻塞
I'm going to run this up in debug mode
我将在调试模式下运行它
and then just refresh that again and
然后再次刷新
let's look at the threads this time so
这次我们来看一下线程
another interesting point so our stack
另一个有趣的地方是我们的堆栈
is way deeper but our threads are like
更深，但是我们的线程就像
way less so we actually have reactor
少一点，所以我们实际上有反应堆
HTTP threads here so you can see we've
HTTP线程在这里，您可以看到我们已经
got eight of those and then the one that
有八个，然后那个
we're being served on is HTTP and i/o -
我们正在使用的是HTTP和I / O-
let's just carry on running and then the
让我们继续运行，然后
remaining ones all happen on this nifty
剩下的都发生在这个漂亮的地方
event loop thing so they all just happen
事件循环的事情，所以他们都发生
straight away and each of those calls
马上，每个电话
the the system can deal with other
该系统可以处理其他
things in between them is like totally
他们之间的事物就像完全
non rocking in the way that it works
不以其运作方式摇摆
okay ah anything I've missed just go
好吧，我想念的任何东西都可以去
check
校验
oh yeah security so I mentioned that
哦，是的，所以我提到了
there are reactive equivalents of most
有大多数的反应当量
of the projects spring security is quite
春季项目的安全性相当
interesting because it's it's reactive
有趣，因为它是反应性的
and nonreactive support is in the same
和无反应的支持是在同一
package so you don't actually need to
包装，因此您实际上并不需要
add a separate starter for that and
为此添加一个单独的启动器，然后
there's no separate like - reactive
没有单独的类似-反应式
security module to use yeah I think
安全模块使用是的，我认为
that's all good let's finish up we've
很好，让我们结束吧
got about five ten minutes left and I
还剩五十分钟，我
want to end by sharing you something
想通过分享一些东西来结束
else that's new and that's micrometer
否则这是新的，那是千分尺
support so let's just run this up again
支持，让我们再次运行它
if we go back to our actuator endpoints
如果我们回到执行器端点
again and look at metrics oh yeah this
再次查看指标哦，是的
is a new login screen because we're
是一个新的登录屏幕，因为我们
using we're flux now but the details are
使用我们现在是变化的，但细节是
the same so our metric stuff has changed
一样，所以我们的指标发生了变化
significantly in boot two and we're no
明显在第二引导，我们不是
longer providing any kind of metrics
不再提供任何指标
library ourselves instead we're relying
我们自己去图书馆
on a project called micrometer and you
在一个名为千分尺的项目上，您
can see the out of the box if you hit
可以看到开箱即用的内容
metrics you kind of get this list of
您可以获取此指标列表的指标
things that you can find out more out so
你可以找到更多的东西
let me pick HTTP server requests for
让我选择HTTP服务器的请求
instance I like it dig into that one a
实例我喜欢它挖到一个
little bit more and I get like basic in
多一点，我变得像基本
memory metrics for for this stuff which
这个东西的内存指标
is kind of it's nice you can still hit
很好，你仍然可以打
the adjacent and look at stuff if you
相邻的，看看东西，如果你
want but one of the real nice parts
想要但真正的好零件之一
about micrometer is if it has like
大约千分尺是
really good integration with lots of
与很多
different libraries like data dog you
像数据狗一样的不同库
know lots of third-party ones and what I
知道很多第三方的，我有什么
want to do show you Prometheus so I'm
想向您展示普罗米修斯，所以我
going to change this app and I'm going
要改变这个程序，我要
to add a new runtime dependency and I'm
添加一个新的运行时依赖项，我
going to call it reactor not reactor
将其称为反应堆而不是反应堆
when we talk about micrometer registry
当我们谈论千分尺注册表时
so these are all that you can see here
这些就是您在这里可以看到的全部
these are all the registries that
这些都是注册管理机构
micrometer supports so I'm just going to
千分尺支撑，所以我只是要
pick the Prometheus one make it a one
选择普罗米修斯一个使它成为一个
time dependency
时间依赖性
now the way that Prometheus works is it
现在普罗米修斯的工作方式是
kind of calls your app so you it hits an
会调用您的应用程序，以便您点击
endpoint and tries to get some data so I
端点并尝试获取一些数据，所以我
need to tweak my security configuration
需要调整我的安全配置
otherwise Prometheus isn't going to be
否则普罗米修斯不会
able to find it so I'm going to add
能够找到它，所以我要添加
another match another endpoint request
另一个匹配另一个端点请求
match and this time to a specific end
比赛，这次到特定的终点
point and micrometer actually will set
点和千分尺实际上会设定
one up for me for Prometheus so I just
一个给我买普罗米修斯，所以我只是
need to spell it correctly so give me
需要正确拼写，所以给我
the PE r om e th e right I know why all
我正确地知道为什么
these are metric tools need to be so
这些是公制工具
difficult to spell so I'm going to do
很难拼写，所以我要去做
that as permit all so I'm just saying
允许的话，我只是说
right you can hit this endpoint that's
对，你可以击中这个终点
fine and all the other end points are
很好，其他所有终点
still authenticated now we don't have a
仍然通过身份验证，现在我们没有
method in here so this this matcher has
方法在这里，所以这个匹配器有
got a nice method called excluding which
有一个很好的方法叫排除
which means that we should be able to
这意味着我们应该能够
use like endpoint to endpoint excluding
使用类似端点到端点排除
prometheus unfortunately in too early we
不幸的是，普罗米修斯为时过早
for some reason made that method package
由于某种原因使该方法包
private by mistake so you have to wait
误将其设为私人，因此您必须等待
for 201 before you can actually use that
才可以实际使用201
one but this will do the same job okay I
一个，但这会做同样的工作好吗
want to do a few other things I want to
想做我想做的其他事情
give some labels to this thing so
给这个东西加一些标签
micrometer is multi-dimensional metrics
千分尺是多维指标
which means that you can kind of give
这意味着你可以给
things labels and you can slice your
东西标签，你可以切你的
application various different ways to
应用各种不同的方式
find out you know which which metrics
找出您知道哪些指标
are behaving like a common one is data
表现得像普通的一样是数据
center you might say let me look at all
您可能会说让我看看所有的中心
the successful requests from you know
您知道的成功请求
the US region one versus u.s. region two
美国一区与美国二区
I'm going to use a meter registry
我要使用电表注册表
customizer which is a special type that
定制程序是一种特殊的类型
you can use to kind of customize meter
你可以用来定制仪表
registries so I'm just going to create a
注册表，因此我将创建一个
B in fact I'm going to add some common
B实际上我将添加一些常见的
tanks that I want in
我想要的战车
let's return an implementation which is
让我们返回一个实现
just a registry gets passed in and I'm
只是注册表被传入而我
going to do registry config dot common
要做注册表配置点常见
tags and some tag pairs I'm going to add
标签和一些标签对，我要添加
an application Swan and webinar okay so
天鹅和网络研讨会的应用程序还可以
that should just add these tanks to
只需将这些战车添加到
everything that micrometer does a few
千分尺所做的一切
more things that I need to do just very
我需要做的更多事情
quickly are I want to add some I'm going
我想快速添加一些我要去的东西
to change some properties so let's do
更改一些属性，让我们开始
percentiles histogram so I'm going to
百分比直方图，所以我要
kind of set up some additional things so
设置了一些其他的东西，所以
this is like a setting that's basically
这就像是一个基本上
saying this this is the prefix and this
说这是前缀和这个
is the name of the metric so HTP server
是指标的名称，因此HTP服务器
requests and I want to want to just send
请求，我只想发送
to a percentile histogram information
百分比直方图信息
back with that and I want to send the
回来，我想发送
Nestle a as well
雀巢也是
- one okay all right I think I think
-好的，我想我认为
we're good
我们很好
someone this again I'm going to go back
再次有人，我要回去
to our actuator end points and make sure
到我们的执行器终点，并确保
that we've got a Prometheus one so we
我们有一个普罗米修斯的，所以我们
have got a Prometheus end point and if
有一个普罗米修斯的终点，如果
we click this you'll see this is the
我们单击此，您将看到这是
data that actually Prometheus scrapes so
Prometheus实际抓取的数据
Prometheus will hit this and find out
普罗米修斯将击中并找出
some stuff so let's maybe hit the cities
一些东西，所以让我们也许去城市
a few times and refresh that you'll see
几次并刷新，您将看到
that these values kind of change well
这些价值观改变得很好
maybe you won't a bit they they do
也许你不会他们做的
change it's just we've got so many that
改变，只是我们有这么多
it's hard to see let's go ahead and
很难看到我们继续前进，
there's a couple of I've got a couple of
有几个我有几个
scripts here I've got a couple of docker
这里的脚本我有几个码头工人
things set up so I'm going to start
设置好了，所以我要开始
Prometheus real and I'm going to start
普罗米修斯真实，我要开始
performer which is like a nice dashboard
表演者，就像一个不错的仪表板
let's see if we can hit that
让我们看看是否可以实现目标
you
您
so I've got a dashboard set up so he can
所以我已经设置好仪表板，以便他可以
see the kind of information that
看到那种信息
micrometer can can provide out the box
千分尺可以提供开箱即用的功能
we get like kief information will have
我们得到像基夫信息将有
units make it a bit finer five minutes
单位使它更好五分钟
okay and I've got some final thing I
好的，我还有最后一件事
want to do is hit this load test as I've
我想做的就是点击这个负载测试
got a little application here very
在这里有一个小应用
straightforward it uses the web client
它直接使用Web客户端
stuff that I was talking about earlier
我刚才讲的东西
and it just hits the cities endpoint and
只是碰到了城市的终点
randomly sends like a bunch of requests
随机发送一堆请求
so if I - this is spring spring
所以如果我-这是 Spring
application it's um it's using some
应用程序，它正在使用一些
spring boot starters but it's not
spring boot 启动器，但不是
actually a spring boot application it's
实际上是一个 spring boot 应用程序
just a main method just to show you the
只是向您展示的一种主要方法
kind of you can like use this stuff in
那种你可以喜欢用这个东西
your own code even if you're not using
您自己的代码，即使您没有使用
spring boot applications come on let's
Spring Boot应用程序来吧
do targets noticed so this is now
注意到目标，所以现在
pumping data through to that thing so if
泵送数据到那个东西，所以如果
I go back over here yeah you can see
我回到这里是的，你可以看到
that we've got some stuff kind of coming
我们有一些东西要来了
in and what's going on there quite right
进去，那里发生的一切非常正确
because it's stressing the CPU and the
因为这给CPU和
threads I was expecting oh yeah here we
我期待的线程哦，是的，在这里，我们
go
走
so we've got some latency information
所以我们有一些延迟信息
here coming in as well one kind of
这里也有一种
interesting note of this is that you can
有趣的是，您可以
see that the average time is like really
看到平均时间就像
good but if you look at the percentile
很好，但如果您查看百分比
times that you know some of your users
你认识一些用户的时候
are not getting that average experience
没有得到平均经验
so it's something to bear in mind with
所以要牢记
metrics
指标
um the average is not always a good
嗯，平均值并不总是很好
measure and you should check out and
测量，您应该检查并
talk by John Schneider about that
约翰·施耐德（John Schneider）谈到
because he goes into a lot more detail
因为他更详细
on some micrometer stuff and I think
在一些千分尺的东西上，我认为
that is it that is all I wanted to show
这就是我想要展示的一切
you so I'm happy to answer any Q&amp;A if
您，因此我很乐意回答任何问答
there is any fill thank you yes there's
有任何填充，谢谢，是的，有
a
一种
ton on well before we get started and
在我们开始之前就继续前进
just jump right into QA I want to say a
刚进入质量检查，我想说一个
few things for for everyone you know I
给你认识的每个人的几件事
saw a few comments from and feedback
看到了一些评论和反馈
from the audience about sort of why
听众讲讲为什么
we're just sort of jumping in to you
我们只是跳入你的行列
know migrating a a spring boot app
知道迁移Spring Boot应用程序
without a lot of context
没有很多背景
um there's there's tons of other context
嗯，还有很多其他背景
available if you want to read the launch
如果您想阅读发布会可用
blog on the spring dot IO fills launch
Spring dot IO博客发布
blog on the spring dot IO web site I
我在spring dot IO网站上的博客
also just published on some content
也刚刚发布在一些内容上
there's if you look in the attachment
如果你看附件
and links section now in your user
和链接部分现在在您的用户中
interface this is a good time to do that
界面，这是一个很好的时机
there's some related content on you know
您知道一些相关内容
spring boot internals um and at the very
spring boot 内部，嗯，在非常
bottom there's a release blog that goes
底部有一个发布博客
into a little bit more detail about some
进一步了解一些细节
of these incremental scenarios from from
这些增量方案中来自
myself and a little bit of Intel from
我自己和一些来自
rawson story on chef um also there's a
主厨嗯，罗森的故事还有一个
bunch of other resources like the github
一堆其他资源，例如github
repo for the demo Phil's been showing
演示Phil的回购展示
today is linked to from there you can
今天链接到那里，你可以
always come back to the same webinar a
总是回到同一场网络研讨会
URL you used to register and get these
您用来注册并获取这些的URL
as attachments but since you're here
作为附件，但由于您在这里
this is a good time now to click through
现在是点击的好时机
to those things bookmark them or open
将那些东西加为书签或打开
them in another tab um we'd love to hear
他们希望在另一个标签中听到
your feedback if you wouldn't mind
您的反馈意见，如果您不介意的话
taking a moment to drop off and go into
花一点时间下车进入
the feedback from audience tab on and
来自和的“受众群体”标签的反馈
let Phil and myself and Madeira and Andy
让菲尔和我自己，马德拉和安迪
Wilkinson know how how we're doing we'd
威尔金森知道我们如何做
love to hear from you we're going to try
很高兴收到您的来信，我们将尽力
to get to as many of your questions as
尽可能多地回答您的问题
possible we've got about ten minutes um
大概十分钟
we're trying to just cherry-pick the
我们正在尝试摘樱桃
best questions to be honest um and what
诚实的最佳问题嗯，还有什么
we'll do is we will put all of your
我们要做的就是将您所有的
questions into a Google Doc and answer
向Google文档提问并回答
them over the course in the next 48 or
在接下来的48个课程中
72 hours or so and then post them as an
72小时左右，然后将其发布为
attachment to the webinar replay again
再次参加网络研讨会重播
the webinar replay is at the same URL
网络研讨会重播使用相同的URL
you used to register and it will be live
您曾经注册过，它将成为现实
later this afternoon even so for anyone
今天下午晚些时候
who's been asking questions about
谁一直在问有关
recorded content we're looking for
我们正在寻找的录制内容
Phil's source code um you know that that
菲尔的源代码，你知道
should address all of those as well as
应该解决所有这些问题以及
you know if you feel you just jump into
你知道你是否觉得自己只是跳进去
the deep end of the pool with uh with a
游泳池深处，有一个
walkthrough of how to upgrade a simple
如何升级简单的演练
app and you don't really understand the
应用程序，你真的不明白
context around spring boots you oh I'd
spring boot 的背景，你哦，我会
really encourage you to read Phil's
真的鼓励您阅读Phil的
launch blog on spring got a oh and then
春季发布博客了哦，然后
my blog on pivotal do that just went
我关于关键的博客就这样了
live this morning and again the links
今天早上住一次又一次的链接
for those are in the attachments and
对于那些在附件中
links section if you're looking to get a
链接部分，如果您希望获得一个
hold of software you can find the Mabel
您可以在软件中找到Mabel
maven and great Gradle coordinates on
行家和伟大的Gradle坐标
the spring boot project page which is
Spring Boot项目页面是
highly google-able if for some reason
如果出于某些原因，则可在Google上使用
you you are on a military network or a
你在军事网络或
close network of some sort behind 200
200后的某种封闭网络
layers of proxy servers and you need an
层代理服务器，您需要
HTTP download we don't make it easy for
HTTP下载，我们不容易
you to do that but you can get them from
你这样做，但你可以从他们那里
our nightly build server which is
我们的每晚构建服务器是
located at repo dot spring I oh I
我位于回购点Spring
believe Phil did I get that right I
相信菲尔，我做对了我
think it's repo dat spring good eye oh
认为这是 Spring 的好日子哦
yeah so they say that again the Joe's
是的，所以他们又说了乔的
are for the for the nightly builds
适用于夜间构建
actually I'm yeah yeah I mean guys don't
其实我是，是的，我是说男人不
spray in Ohio slash snap shell will give
在俄亥俄州的斜线弹壳喷涂
you the night leases snapshot okay cool
你晚上租借快照好酷
and you can get an HTTP download from
然后您可以从http下载
there if you're like stuck on a military
如果您喜欢被困在军队中
network or or close network all right so
网络或关闭网络都可以
let's get off to some of the questions
让我们开始一些问题
thanks for your patience um some of the
多谢您的耐心等候，
first ones up and Phil we're gonna try
首先，Phil我们将尝试
to go through these fairly breezy on so
经历这些相当微风
you know either mother or auntie or
你知道妈妈还是姨妈
yourself might be jumping in to answer
你自己可能正在回答
some of these but we're gonna go try to
其中一些，但我们要去尝试
keep the answer short so you can get
简短回答，这样您就可以
through a number of them a few people
通过他们中的一些人
asked about spring cloud about when
问Spring Cloud何时
spring boots to Oh will be supported by
spring boot 到哦会得到支持
excuse me when spring cloud is going to
对不起，当 Spring 的云将要
be using spring boot - OH
使用 spring boot -哦
and the answer to that is that Andy I
答案是Andy I
believe you said there was a milestone
相信你说有一个里程碑
eight that already does and then we'll
八个已经完成，然后我们将
have a GA sometime next month
下个月某个时候有通用航空
is that right yeah that's right finish
是的，是的，正确的完成
the master Nate was released just a few
内特大师被释放了
days ago I think built on top of spring
天以前，我认为建在 Spring 之上
group - oh and Mel
组-哦和梅尔
there's some relief candidates become
有一些救济候选人成为
and then I think they're aiming for
然后我认为他们的目标是
mid-april for the Finchley release
Finchley发行的4月中旬
perfect perfect so all you spring cloud
完美完美，让你春意盎然
users you'll be able to get a 2.0 boo
用户，您将能够获得2.0 boo
2.0 compatible version quite quickly um
2.0兼容版本很快
next question is I think this is fulfill
下一个问题是我认为这很满足
on filled is the new binder
在填充是新的粘合剂
functionality work with the at
功能与at
configuration properties annotated
带注释的配置属性
components if we're using at
组件，如果我们在
configuration properties do we need to
配置属性，我们需要
do anything to upgrade yeah so that the
做任何事情升级是的，以便
new binder stuff is what's used like to
新的粘合剂的东西是用来
bind those configuration properties you
绑定那些配置属性
generally speaking won't need to do
一般来说，不需要做
anything to upgrade because like the the
任何升级，因为像
input and output should be the same it's
输入和输出应该相同
just the mechanism we use in the middle
只是我们在中间使用的机制
has changed the only exception is if
改变了唯一的例外是
you're using environment variables the
您正在使用环境变量
format of the environment variables is a
环境变量的格式是
lot stricter than it used to be so just
比以前严格得多
there's a wiki page that kind of
有一个维基页面
describes this in a bit more detail but
更详细地描述了这一点，但是
just take care that basically your dots
只是要注意，基本上你的点
in your property name have to be
在您的财产名称中必须
underscores and you can no longer have
下划线，您将不再拥有
underscores between the case changes in
强调案例之间的变化
the camel cases like name but other than
骆驼的情况像名字，但不是
that it should be transparent awesome
它应该是透明的真棒
thanks on next question was can you
谢谢下一个问题是你
still disable the web security if the
如果
property has gone away I'm not entirely
财产消失了，我还不完全
sure that feels like if a question
确保感觉就像一个问题
fragment but does that make sense to you
碎片，但这对您有意义
that's probably a question that
这可能是一个问题
madhumathi able to answer I think it's
madhumathi能够回答我认为这是
um um yeah so the security not enabled
嗯嗯，所以安全性未启用
flag has gone away and that was because
国旗不见了，那是因为
it was confusing to a lot of people
这让很多人感到困惑
because it only disabled its fault or
因为它仅禁用了故障或
it's a good security but not a few added
这是一个很好的安全性，但没有添加
your own security if you do have spring
如果您有Spring ，请确保自己的安全
security on the classpath and you still
在类路径上的安全性，你仍然
want to say disable it for tests you can
想说禁用它可以测试
use the exclude auto-configuration
使用排除自动配置
thread or string security it also
线程或字符串的安全性
provides a bunch of test hazards so you
提供了很多测试危害，因此您
can do like with mark user and use those
可以与标记用户一起使用并使用
instead of having to disable security
而不是必须禁用安全性
awesome hey thanks mother
太好了，谢谢妈妈
another question was just spring boot -
另一个问题是 spring boot -
currently support WebLogic 12 see any
当前支持WebLogic 12
issues with it that you're aware of I
你知道我的问题
think we could generalize this to also
认为我们可以将其概括为
just talk about the other containers
只是谈论其他容器
that we test on and the question for
我们测试的问题
Andy definitely he's a question of
安迪绝对是他的问题
ratings Beijing Beijing India Nile well
评级北京北京印度尼罗河
wonderful it's always a pleasure to talk
很棒，总是很高兴聊
about AB service and so if you're
关于AB服务，如果您
deploying a springs of war file and
部署战争文件，
Spring Framework 5 and therefore spring
Spring Framework 5，因此是spring
bootie 2.0 require a server 3.1
靴子2.0需要服务器3.1
compatible container which I believe the
我相信兼容的容器
newer versions of WebLogic 12c support
较新版本的WebLogic 12c支持
servlet 3.1
Servlet 3.1
so you should be fine there and recent
所以你应该在那里和最近
versions of have any other container
版本具有任何其他容器
will work and we test on WebSphere
会工作，我们将在WebSphere上进行测试
Liberty GlassFish Tommy's a separate
自由眼镜鱼汤米是一个单独的
standalone Tomcat as part of our build
独立的Tomcat作为我们构建的一部分
so we've got reasonably good coverage a
因此我们的覆盖范围相当广
various server 3.1 containers but it
各种服务器3.1容器，但是
should work on any of any of them that
应该在其中任何一个上工作
claim serve at 3.1 compatibility awesome
声称在3.1兼容性方面表现出色
which ones do we explicitly test with uh
我们用uh明确测试了哪些
where's fear Liberty
在哪里恐惧自由
Tom EE Tomcat Mahalo I think did he
Tom EE Tomcat Mahalo我认为他
heard GlassFish is opposed for four or
听说GlassFish反对四个或
five and then obviously on the three
五，然后显然是三
embedded containers that we support or
我们支持的嵌入式容器或
tomcat jecheon
tomcat jecheon
under - of course of course yep okay
在-当然可以，是的
great hey thanks for that Nady really
非常感谢Nady真的
appreciate it um let's see another
欣赏它，让我们看看另一个
couple other questions on and I'm not
几个其他的问题，我不是
sure for this one is for but a question
肯定这是一个问题
was is there a spring bootie mo migrator
那里有 spring boot 莫移民吗
as our company an inner company we
作为公司内部公司，我们
usually use yeah malls rather than
通常会使用购物中心而不是
properties uh so the properties migrated
属性，所以属性已迁移
I assume that this person is talking
我认为这个人在说话
about the the properties migrated
关于已迁移的属性
dependency and that actually work I
依赖和实际工作我
think oh I think so yeah yeah that works
想想哦，我想是的，是的，可以
actually at the spring-like property
实际上在 Spring 般的财产
level it's not not tied to property
不与财产挂钩
sales so yeah if you have a yeah mall
如果有商场的话就这么卖
source it just gives you exactly the
来源它只是给你确切的
same output it just
同样的输出
points to the line in the ammo file
指向弹药文件中的行
rather than the properties file so yeah
而不是属性文件，是的
that works fine
效果很好
I think okay got it go um okay let's see
我想好了，好吧，让我们看看
we're actually doing okay on on time so
我们实际上准时做得很好，所以
those are some of the critical ones but
这些是一些关键的，但是
there's one thing though is during the
虽然有一件事是
presentation I just wanted to briefly
我只是想简要介绍一下
point out the the actuator stuff you may
指出执行器的东西
you may have noticed that actuator kind
您可能已经注意到执行器种类
of worked when we switch to a reactive
切换到被动式时的工作量
stack and we have this brand-new
堆栈，我们有这个全新的
abstraction now around actuator
现在围绕执行器进行抽象
endpoints and that also means that that
端点，这也意味着
will work with Jersey so if you've had
将与Jersey合作，所以如果您有
to jump through some hoops in the past
跳过过去的篮球
with one-five where you're writing a
有五分之一，你正在写一个
Jersey app that you have spring MVC so
球衣应用，您拥有春季MVC，因此
you can have actuators you can drop
你可以放下执行器
spring MVC entirely now and things will
现在完全MVC Spring ，事情将会
just work got it okay cool um there was
刚刚工作就可以了，很酷，嗯
one question about it was a bit short
关于它的一个问题有点简短
but the question was literally just what
但问题实际上是什么
about jetty over Tomcat on and Andy I
关于Tomcat和Andy I上的码头
think you had to a commenter who you
认为你必须向评论员证明你是谁
wanted to say on that one um I guess
我想说那一嗯
this was a question about using web
这是关于使用网络的问题
swaps on top of a an embedded servlet
在嵌入式servlet顶部交换
container so still shows the app running
容器，因此仍显示应用程序正在运行
on top of on top of Tomcat and and the
在Tomcat之上，并且
be clever kind of adapting stuff that
聪明地适应
spring MVC does and to turn to deal with
Spring MVC做并转向处理
mono and flux on top of a servlet
servlet顶部的mono和flow
container you can do that on top of any
容器，您可以在任何容器之上执行此操作
container is just using this surf at 3.1
容器仅在3.1使用此冲浪
async stuff you get a seed and do a know
异步的东西，你会得到种子并知道
kind of a full web clocks app on top of
有点像完整的网络时钟应用
Tomcat jetty or undertow any of the
Tomcat码头或拖曳任何
embedded containers because we hook into
嵌入式容器，因为我们将其插入
the servlet the async stuff in the
Servlet中的异步内容
servlet API so then the question of
servlet API，那么接下来的问题
jetty versus Tomcat just comes down to
码头对雄猫只是归结为
your personal preference really what
你的个人喜好到底是什么
what containing almost familiar with in
包含几乎熟悉的内容
which one you prefer yep
是您更喜欢哪一个
and I think along that same lines there
我认为同样的思路
there was a question about you know um
有一个关于你知道的问题
because I think you're kind of halfway
因为我认为你有点中途
there already right and the question was
已经正确了，问题是
what about you know there no servlet
你怎么知道没有servlet
support for reactive Web Apps you know
支持您知道的反应式Web Apps
what what's the equivalent and you and I
什么是等效的，你我
were discussing this in the chat saying
在聊天中讨论这个问题
to help servlet and what flux are
帮助servlet和什么通量
fundamentally different api's but yeah
根本不同的api，但是
yeah that's pretty much covers it
是的，这几乎涵盖了它
because if if you're writing your web
因为如果您正在编写网络
flux app and you want to use the non
助焊剂应用程序，您想使用非
blocking stuff then you can't write
阻止东西，那么你不能写
servlets because IO is inherently
servlet，因为IO本质上是
blocking it has to deal with Indian
阻止它必须与印度人打交道
streams and things so the equivalent I
流和东西，所以相当于我
guess would either be the annotation
猜测可能是注释
based filtering model that Phil showed
Phil展示的基于过滤的模型
using rest controller and controller and
使用剩余控制器和控制器，以及
get mapping and whatnot or this the
得到映射和诸如此类的东西
functional side of web flocks which Phil
网状群的功能性方面
didn't show but there are there's a blog
没有显示，但是有一个博客
post about it on the bottom sure we can
在底部发布有关它的信息，我们一定可以
add a link to that and it shows another
添加一个链接到它，它显示了另一个
another alternative programming model if
另一个替代编程模型，如果
you're if you're not fond of annotations
如果您不喜欢注释
awesome thanks nearly Phil is it
很棒的感谢，几乎是菲尔
possible to export that graph in our
可以在我们的图中导出该图
dashboard configuration so it can be
仪表板配置，因此可以
shared
共享
I don't know heart of that fitting that
我不知道那种适合的心
github repo so it is okay yeah there's a
github repo所以没关系，是的
desert there's a couple if you go to the
沙漠里有一对夫妇，如果你去
github repo looking at my comments a
github回购看我的评论
folder there's the load tester and some
文件夹中有负载测试器和一些
scripts to start up both that profiler
启动两个探查器的脚本
and the the Prometheus and there's a
和普罗米修斯，还有一个
JSON file but it just imports so you
JSON文件，但它只是导入，因此您
just have to run a couple of scripts and
只需运行几个脚本，然后
and they they will basically it will
他们基本上会
start up a docker container and import
启动一个Docker容器并导入
that dashboard so you can do what you
该仪表板，以便您可以做自己的事
want with it
想要它
awesome ok I think we have time for
棒极了，我想我们有时间
literally one more question I think it's
从字面上看，我认为这是另外一个问题
time to wrap up on and I think this one
是时候总结了，我认为这是
is interesting Phil and excuse me uh
是有趣的菲尔，对不起
Mindy and mother--i if we have one more
明迪和母亲-如果我再有一个的话
is there a spring boot starter JPA
是否有Spring 启动启动器JPA
reactive dependency particular in
反应依赖
particular is there support for paging
特别是是否支持分页
and also with the JPA api
以及JPA api
no ok hi Barry and as far as on the way
不，嗨，巴里，就在途中
like that again it's like the
再次像那样
fundamental difference between between
之间的根本区别
Webb flux and web MVC is you know hi
Webb Flux和Web MVC是您知道的吗
Nate is currently very much built on a
内特目前很大程度上建立在
bond there is no like reactive JDBC as
绑定没有像反应式JDBC那样的
yet you know there are some drivers like
但是你知道有些司机喜欢
I think Postgres has got one like a
我认为Postgres有一个像
reactive support but there's no reactive
反应性支持，但没有反应性
JDBC so there's no way of building a
JDBC，因此无法构建一个
reactive hibernate and there's no
反应性冬眠，没有
reactive JPA so there's no way I can I
反应性的JPA，所以我无法
think that spring data can currently
认为 spring data 目前可以
offer that I know someone was actually
提供我知道有人实际上是
asking sorry I was gone
问抱歉我走了
know somebody was actually asking about
知道有人在问
the Oracle reactive gtb/c driver efforts
Oracle反应性gtb / c驱动程序的工作
as well and I think I think those are
以及我认为我认为这些是
still pretty nascent and just feed
还很新生，只是喂
directly into what you were saying so I
直接进入你所说的，所以我
think we got two questions there with
认为我们在那里有两个问题
one yeah sorry I didn't mean some truck
是的，对不起，我不是说要卡车
you know yeah I was going to say the
你知道是的，我要说的是
same thing I believe that I believe that
我相信，我相信
there are some efforts underway to start
有一些努力正在开始
you know in Oracle with a reactive JDBC
您知道在Oracle中使用响应式JDBC
and my guess is that the order you'll
我的猜测是您要订购
see things in is probably like once that
看到里面的东西大概就是一次
happens I imagine spring data will be
发生我想像 Spring 的数据将
able to offer like JDBC star support
能够提供类似JDBC star的支持
before JPA catches up but yeah it's a
在JPA赶上之前，是的，
fairly 50/50 second warning we're
相当50/50秒的警告
literally gonna get we're running out of
字面上会让我们耗尽
time for questions so folks what we're
是时候提问了，乡亲们我们是什么
going to do is if we didn't get you a
要做的是，如果我们没有给你一个
question don't worry we internally will
问题不要担心我们内部会
sort of share that in a Google Doc and
在Google文档中分享的内容，以及
work on the answers over the next you
在下一个你的答案上工作
know 48 72 hours and we'll post them as
知道48 72小时，我们将其发布为
an attachment all the ones that we can't
所有我们无法做到的附件
answer we'll do our best to make sure if
回答我们会尽力确保
you entered your question that we will
您输入了问题，我们将
get to it and we'll be posted as a
做到这一点，我们将以
attachment to the webinar we play which
参加网络研讨会的附件
is again at that same URL you used to
再次使用您以前使用的相同网址
register so listen thank you very much
注册所以听非常感谢
everyone for joining Phil really
大家真的加入了Phil
appreciate it mother--i and II really
妈妈，很感激-我和我真的
think thanks a lot for jumping in and
非常感谢您加入，
helping field all the questions um and
帮助回答所有问题，嗯，
we hope you go out and build some
我们希望你出去建造一些
amazing things with spring boot and I
我和 spring boot 让我感到惊奇
think you know we're gonna we're in a
以为你知道我们要去
great position so we'll see you at the
位置很好，我们会在
next webinar thanks for coming
下一次网络研讨会感谢您的光临
you
您